And we are just one game away from
milestone four.
Oh, yeah.
All right, now we're against the John
Doe. That'll be pretty cool if we get
like an LMS in this game. I don't know
if we will though. Right now, since the
game did just start and the John Doe's
probably setting up footprints, we can
go do a generator if there's one
available. Yeah, let's just uh finish up
this one, but then we'll start helping
the team really quickly.
That's the milestone four one, too.
There we go. Nice.
Now, where is the killer? Oh, shoot.
He's right there.
Okay.
Uh what's he doing? Is he setting up a
footprint? That's a free crystal right
there. Put himself in the building.
Just look for like those times when the
killer is like using an ability and
that's a free crystal. I'm going to try
to find an opportunity to slash here,
too, if possible.
If we can get the perfect timing here,
there we go. That doesn't happen uh that
doesn't activate their unstoppable. They
might have been able to dodge it, but
it's really hard to cuz of the lunge.
Make sure when you're stunning a John
Doe using spikes to
not stun them like during the wind up
cuz then it'll activate unstoppable and
that kind of makes matters worse. You
got to like find that like
it's hard to find the perfect timing,
but there's like perfect timing where
they can't dodge it and it still stuns
them, which is really beneficial.
Are they after us right now? Yeah, they
are.
Okay, where
I honestly could have crystal that. I
should have.
I'm just going to do it right now.
>> [groaning]
>> It's getting pretty close. Oh, shoot. I
didn't see the spikes.
I might use it around the corner here. I
don't know, actually.
Oh, yeah. See, they activated
unstoppable. That makes it worse.
Or maybe they just reacted to it. I
don't know if they were actually using
spikes there.
Let's see though. Let's get
Okay, we applied resonance. Oh, we
activated the unstoppable again.
It's not too good. Not too good.
Great. Let's go over here.
There's no resonance right now, but
Okay, they use spikes there.
Sometimes you can just use your hatchet
without the resonance.
To honestly help the team.
Applied some resonance there.
Okay, the Shulski healed up. That's
really good. They might start getting
trapped here. No, the John Doe's not
zoning.
All right, spamming that resonance on
them.
We keep stunning the freaking
I can't tell if if he's unstoppable
parrying or if we're stunning the spikes
over and over.
All right, I just realized he's stunning
me now. That's really stupid.
Yeah, like he just keeps spamming the
spikes.
Yeah, that's a really stupid crystal
thorn on my part.
Okay, that was a good
shot if you didn't parry. Yeah, he
didn't parry.
Okay, that guy dropped down there.
Got to try to
help him out.
Okay, yeah, he's using spikes.
Perfect timing.
That should be perfect.
I can't tell if that if that was perfect
or not. I might have been a bit early.
All right, who's getting chased right
now?
They're like down here.
But that's okay. The round's about to
end. That was milestone four, though.
Let's go.
Cannot wait to use this skin. This looks
so cool.
Just look at this lineup, bro. John Doe
milestone four, Jane Doe milestone four.
So good together. Okay, we're against
the Noli. Noli gets hard-countered by
uh Jane Doe cuz your hatchet, even if
there's no resonance, you can just hit
it at one of their re-rushes and they
can't re-rush. So,
yeah, just you can always stop their
void rush pretty much.
Okay, then we got that generator done
really quick. Dude, look at this.
Oh my gosh, this is so good. This is so
good. Where is the Nolly?
Are they AFK?
People are kind of lining up here like
they're AFK. Oh, no, they are not.
All right, we'll just get a crystal off
that if they're not going to
All right, nice. I thought they still
were still after that.
Um See, they don't have any resonance
right now. I don't know if I really want
to use my hatchet.
The guy's not in that dire situation. I
could just wait for my resonance.
See.
I'm going to
start charging it here.
There we go. I got some resonance on
them.
Uh I wasn't positioned there for the
for the M lag.
Just going to follow this guy, make the
Nolly scared of my stun.
Just going to get some resonance on
them.
If they start climbing up here, it's
harder for them to dodge, so we can do
that.
It's very nice.
Hopped out the newb.
And just like staying on top of the
survivor who's being chased applies a
lot of pressure.
All right, I got some resonance on them.
They're already resonance three. They do
need to nerf that about Jane Doe or at
least bug fix it. You're not meant to be
able to apply resonance that fast.
Um oh, they teleported up there.
They did not want to climb those stairs,
dude.
Um
That's the real one? Yeah, that's the
real one.
Okay, applied resonance.
Try to get this M lag.
There we go.
Oh, the custom hatchet animation, too. I
didn't even see that.
That's so good, dude.
All right. Where
Let's wait for that spawn symbol to go
away, and then we should be able to do
that. That'll give purified, too. I
should really look for my purified
opportunities, but you can only do it
later in the game since it's only really
good when they're uh lower HP. Look,
guys, if you know how the purified
works, it's like
uh the lower HP they are, the more
resistance they'll get.
So, yeah, we haven't really been able to
use it yet. Maybe soon with the
Shedletsky.
I kind of want to just apply a
resonance, though.
All right, they got a free hit on me.
Yeah, I probably should have been more
careful about that.
There we go, that's a free stun around
the corner.
Got a shadow point back from when they
got a free hit on us.
Let's see, where are they? Oh, wait, no,
the Shedletsky, the Shedletsky.
All right, we're going against the 1x
this time. Let's get some generators
done just a little bit before we start
helping the team. Of course, again, as
Jane Doe, you do want to be very active
in helping the team.
But, uh two generators doesn't hurt.
Takes off six seconds off the clock.
But, now let's actually try to help.
Um that should be a free crystal.
I barely got that. I should not have got
that, actually. I did that way too late.
Ooh, they missed the stun, that sucks.
We've got to like really help them out,
they're kind of dying.
And we can apply purified. Oh, that
person applied purified. It's really
good.
I can apply purified to them soon if uh
Here, I'll give them purified.
That person got the stun off. I was
considering doing the stun, but I was
just going to let someone else do it so
I could be here to give purified cuz not
many other people do that. Like I'll let
the other people do the stunning.
Ooh, they've got to be really careful
here. This is really bad position to be
in. I don't know why they went here.
Ooh, that sucks. All right, we got to
get out ourselves.
Might go with that century if things
start getting a bit desperate.
Oh wait, they switched targets.
Oh, they didn't keep moving.
All right, it's fine. All right, let's
uh get away from there so it's easier to
dodge.
Yeah, yeah, they switched targets.
Um I have no idea what they're
Anyway.
Let's
see.
Just going to apply some resonance there
so we can actually stun them.
Whenever Mmal'Goth is using mass
infection, try to get like as much
distance as you can from them. There we
go. We got a stun around the corner.
They didn't expect it.
Doing stuns around corners is really
just like the most consistent way to
land your stuns. Doing it out in the
open I mean just they're pretty much
just like any other stun mobile.
Uh okay, we kind of cornered ourselves
with that, but it's okay. They're not on
us.
See, I'm going to try to get a crystal
off here.
There we go.
Ooh.
Okay, nice. We didn't get hit.
Oh, they got hit. That really sucks. We
got to protect them now.
We probably should be ready to apply
purified if needed.
And they're like planning to just like
projectile jump scare right now, aren't
they?
Yeah.
I changed the elevation.
Are they just going to keep doing that?
Okay, wait. Hold on.
Okay, I've got to be really Give them
purified. No! Why did they go for a
stun?
Actually, Uh, guess that was better for
them, but shoot.
Okay, hold on.
Man, we could have applied purified to
them. That would have been really good.
Up the stairs is harder to dodge. Yeah.
It's a bit more narrow.
And we got to be careful though.
Um, when should I go for a crystal? I'm
going to wait for them to drain their
stamina a little bit more just so it's
easier to hit.
Next to that wall should be nice. Oh, we
gave them purified too. That helped them
tank a little Actually, no, it didn't.
no, it didn't. They were not low
enough HP for it.
Are they going to die?
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
We've got to be really careful. There's
2 minutes. Uh, if possible, I'd like to
start my chase over here for the
elevation.
Let's just lob this at them.
Now, what are they planning, dude?
They're going to like
All right, let's go down here.
Got to be really careful.
I kind of want to stay close to them
just so I can do that.
Yeah, cuz the thing about that, you can
tank them as infection and then heal it
back from the shadow point you get with
the axe. So, don't be too scared to If
If you know like if you know you're
guaranteed like definitely going to hit
that axe, remember you're going to get
the shadow point after. So, you can
honestly just like tank stuff and heal
it back with the axe.
It's something I like to do. You saw me
just do it. Uh, let me chain over here.
I don't want to run into that sentry
yet. I'm not in too much danger right
now.
Uh, let me like He might be wiping it
out. Oh, he didn't wipe it out.
Uh,
let's be very careful. If he entangles,
I could honestly do the hatchet like
just like stun stack against one X.
Oh, that was It's prediction. Holy cow.
Oh, I did not mean to stagger on there.
Okay, I might have to start running to
the sentry soon. I lost a lot of stamina
with that.
Just going to run really far away and
you could easily dodge that.
Let's get a crystal on them.
Resonance three is pretty crazy. We got
hit by that but we're behind the wall so
it's fine.
I might start running to the sentry
soon.
Uh that's fine.
Or actually, I have a plan. I have a
plan.
Where are they?
Where are they going?
Oh, they're after the building men now.
Yeah, the building men probably is worth
it. I got to protect this guy.
Okay.
Where are they? Where are they?
I can't stun them there. They're in like
the killer wall.
This is really sketchy.
I reapplied resonance.
This is really sketchy, dude.
Okay, dodge that.
There's only 10 seconds left. I might
just go for a greedy stun here.
Where'd they go?
The heck?
Like started running all the way over
there.
But yeah, there we go.
Pretty good pretty good uh
pretty good solo survival there.
Ooh, and that's route two. You don't see
that too often.
Um let's uh we can do generator right
now.
We got to be really careful though. I'm
going to try to like have my camera a
bit peeked at the sky in case Nest route
two tries to do something.
Oh yeah, that's see them. I see them.
Is that a free crystal? I don't know. I
don't know the I-frames on Nest route
two that well.
Um
Oh, they're going to try to
Okay, yeah. Thank goodness.
Dodge that.
Yeah, I don't know the I frames on the
strategy that well. I don't know how
much of his frames I give that. So, this
might be a bit awkward with the crystal.
Going to try to play resonance here.
Oh, that really sucks.
I'm going to like actually like punish
their end like or something. I'm not
hitting these crystals.
Okay, there. And that right now. Oh,
they hit the ghast.
Okay.
Uh can I apply purify to that? I missed.
No way.
Let me just Let's not stunning them, but
they can kind of use it right now just a
little bit of slowness.
Oh, goodness. Okay.
Yeah, I've not been hitting my crystals.
They're actually like dodging them
pretty well.
We're going to like find better times to
throw it.
We're trying to get over there.
Wait, what are they doing?
I don't know where they are.
Over there?
Oh, crap.
Okay, it's hard for them to Oh, where
did they go?
I was going to say it's harder for them
to dodge at the fence, but
You can probably do it here. Yeah, they
didn't see around the corner.
Okay.
Oh, no, I'm lagging. No, stop. Stop.
Dude, if I come back and I'm dead
I'm poisoned? Where did I get poisoned?
I was expecting like my HP to go down,
not that I got poisoned. What?
>> [snorts]
>> Okay, that's sad.
Um
Oh, what's that?
Oh, they did bat mode. What the heck?
Just dodged it that way.
Okay, hold on.
I got to like be more there, honestly.
Oh, and they killed someone.
Never mind.
I'm going to do a generator right now.
Can we Oh, no, we can't.
Kind of being zoned into here right now.
I want to get resonance two on them.
Okay, they dodged it that way. Kind of
just got to whip that out. Resonance is
about to run out.
See, I'm going to sit on top OF THE
GUEST.
WHAT? WHAT?
WHY DID THE GUEST GET HIT? WHAT?
I have no clue what happened there.
Okay, hold on. Let me go over here. I
want to loop back to the team, though.
They're low stamina. Should be harder
for them to dodge that.
What? This guest's like priority I need
to go here right now.
This guest's like hit priority doesn't
work, dude. He tried to block there, it
didn't block. Oh, no.
Okay.
I might have been able to go stun that,
but I don't really want to right now.
Yeah, let's go back to the team.
Get a little crystal thrown there.
Splashed on the wall, so that was nice.
We have resonance three right now.
That's really good.
Let me try there.
All right, this is kind of bad.
Oh, they didn't go after me. I was kind
of trapped.
Hit that one on them, too.
Oh, they're trying to kill the guest.
All right, can I stun that? Oh, we can.
Nice.
There we go. Pretty good teamwork that
game, actually.
Pretty good teamwork.
And that right there
is milestone for Jane Doe.
Peace out, guys. Have a good day.
>> [music]